The moon shook
And curled up like gentle fire
The ocean glazed
And melted wire
Voices buzzed in spiral eyes
Stars dived in blinding skies
Stars die
Blinding skies
Tree cracked
And mountain cried
Bridges broke
And window sighed
Cells grew up and rivers burst
Sound obscured and sense reversed
Stars die
Blinding skies
Because of what you have done, the heavens have become a part of man's world
And as you talk to us from the Sea of Tranquility, it inspires us to redouble our efforts to bring peace and tranquility to Earth
Idle mind
And severed soul
Silent nerves
And begging bowl
Shallow haze to blast a way
Hyper sleep to end the day
Stars die
Blinding skies